export const questions = [
    {
        "question": "What does CPU stand for?",
        "choices": [
            "Computer personal unit",
            "Central process unit",
            "Central processing unit",
            "Central processor unit"
        ],
        "correct": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "ALU stands for",
        "choices": [
            "Arithimatic Logic unit",
            "Application logic unit",
            "Array logic unit",
            "None of the above"
        ],
        "correct": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The brain of any computer system is",
        "choices": [
            "ALU",
            "CPU",
            "None of the above",
            "Memory",
            "Control Unit"
        ],
        "correct": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "What difference does 5th generation computer have from other generation computers?",
        "choices": [
            "Technological advncement",
            "Object oriented programming",
            "Scientific code",
            "All of the above"
        ],
        "correct": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following computer generation uses concept of artificial intelligence?",
        "choices": [
            "First generation",
            "Second generation",
            "Third generation",
            "Fourth generation"
        ],
        "correct": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "When a key is pressed on the keyboard, which standard is used to convert the keysroke to corrosponding bits?",
        "choices": [
            "ANSI",
            "ANSCII",
            "EBCDIC",
            "ISO"
        ],
        "correct": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Which device is useed as standard pointing device in a graphical user environment?",
        "choices": [
            "Keyboard",
            "Mouse",
            "Joystick",
            "Trackball"
        ],
        "correct": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following is a valid storage type?",
        "choices": [
            "CPU",
            "Keyboard",
            "Control Unit",
            "ALU"
        ],
        "Correct": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "A list of coded instructions is called",
        "choices": [
            "Computer program",
            "Algorithm",
            "Flowchart",
            "Utility program"
        ],
        "correct": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Any storage device added to computer beyond the immediately usable main storage is known as",
        "choices": [
            "Floppy disk",
            "Hard disk",
            "Backing store",
            "Punched card"
        ],
        "correct": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following is not a input device?",
        "choices": [
            "Touchpad",
            "Mouse",
            "Printer",
            "Keyboard"
        ],
        "correct": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following is a system software?",
        "choices": [
            "Linux",
            "Word",
            "Excel",
            "Tally"
        ],
        "correct": 0
    }
];